字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
为了阻止邪恶极速者萨维塔
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
我不小心闯入了未来
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
看到他杀死了我心爱的女人
and I saw him murder the woman I love.
但是我不会再让这事发生了
But I won't let that happen.
我会尽我一切的努力
I'm going to do everything in my power
来改变未来
to change the future,
而我是唯一来得及拯救她的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
尖端科研实验室
爆裂观光活动
你想让尖端科研实验室对大众公开吗
You wanna open S.T.A.R. Labs to the public?
-两个星期后吗  -小型的开张典礼
- In two weeks? - Soft open.
我是炼金术师
I'm Alchemy.
你把无辜的人变成
Turning innocent people
超能力者  膜拜那个萨维塔
into meta-humans worshipping the Savitar?
闪电侠在危机中消失
原本是爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦写的报道
An article used to be written by Iris West-Allen.
由朱莉·格里尔撰写
我们的未来有所改变了
Something's changed with our future.
-巴里  -不要
- Barry. - No!
你看到的是未来的一种可能
What you saw was one possibility of the future.
那么我可以阻止它发生了吗
Then I can stop this from happening.
我不明白  这是哪里
I--I don't understand. Where are we?
家  我不知道
Home. I don't know...
未来会怎样
what's gonna happen in the future.
我只知道此时此地
All I know is right here, right now,
我要跟你一起度过所有时光
I wanna spend every moment I can with you.
不要
Don't!
-不要这么做  -巴里
- Don't do this! - Barry--
你输了  巴里
You lose, Barry.
不
No!
宝贝  你还好吗
Babe, are you okay?
-没事  -好吧
- Yeah... - Yeah.
只是做了个噩梦
Just a bad dream.
继续睡吧
Go back to sleep.
哦  就好像听到你大喊之后
Yeah, sure. I'm not completely wide awake
我还能睡着似的
after hearing you scream in your sleep.
你想不想聊聊
You wanna talk about it?
不想  你知道我想做什么吗
No, you know what I wanna do?
我要去打开行李
I'm gonna unpack.
已经一个月了
It's been a month.
别转移话题  巴塞洛缪
Do not change the subject, Bartholomew.
巴塞洛缪
Bartholomew?
我有麻烦了吗
Am I in trouble?
这已经是连续第三个晚上了
Well, this is the third night in a row.
我还知道连续三晚发生了什么
I know something else that's happened three nights in a row.
着火了
It's a fire.
里士满海茨
Richmond Heights.
去吧  要不沃利会比你先到的
Go, Wally's gonna beat you there.
-怎么了  -我只是
- What? - I just...
我真的很爱你
I just really love you.
帕特森警探刚刚进去
Detective Patterson just ran inside.
他还没有出来
He hasn't come out yet.
消防队已经无法及时赶到了
The fire department will not make it here on time.
救命
Help!
我被困在这了
I'm trapped in here!
我们得把他救出去
We gotta get him out of here.
这地方随时都可能被大火吞噬
This place is up in flames any second.
-你看到门周围的黑烟了吗  -看到了
- You see the soot around this door? - Yeah.
因为这里没有空气流通
'Cause the fire has no ventilation,
所以如果我们打开了门
so if we open the door now,
突然进入的氧气会造成爆炸
the sudden inrush of oxygen will cause an explosion.
救命
Help!
好吧  那我们该怎么做
Okay, so what do we do?
给热气和烟创造一个出口
Create an exit point for the heat and smoke,
并在同时带走氧气
and remove all the oxygen at the same time.
-这样就能灭火了  -救救我
- Which will put out the fire. - Help me!
听我的命令  再打开门  好吧
When I say so, open the door, all right?
就现在
Now.
闪电侠  谢谢你
Flash, thanks.
两个闪电侠
Two of 'em.
闪电侠
第三季
第十集
你太酷了  你怎么能那么冷静
Oh, man, that was so dope. How do you stay so calm?
你简直太从容了
You're like scary calm in the middle of a fight.
这就是经验  沃利
It's just experience, Wally.
所以你不要太冲动  好好学学
That's why it's important for you to shadow me for a while,
我的经验  这很重要
and try to learn everything I know.
然后我就能大展身手了
And then I get to kick some ass.
我给你点建议吧  沃利
Let me give you some advice, Wally.
作为超级英雄不只是要打击坏蛋
Being a superhero's not about kicking ass.
也不是  其实那是个大谎言
Well... nope, actually that's a straight-up lie.
当然要打击坏蛋
There's a lot of ass-kicking involved.
你只要继续坚持下去
Just keep doing what you're doing--
看着我  你做得非常好
Watching me. You're doing great.
我要去和老爸吃早餐了
I gotta go to breakfast with Dad,
但是我晚点会来找你们的
but I'll catch up with you guys later.
那是...  算了
Yo, that's where--  mm-- Nope.
-你没事吧  -我的战衣放那里
- You okay? - My suit goes there.
两套战衣  一个人体模型
Ah, two suits, one mannequin.
这下有难题了
That is what we call a conundrum.
不  我
No, I--
你没事吧
Hey, are you okay?
最近这些东西总是出故障
Yeah, these things have just been on the fritz lately.
让我觉得自己像个罪犯
It makes me feel like a criminal.
没有出故障
Hasn't been on the fritz, okay?
或许像我告诉你的  去充充电
Uh, maybe if you charge the battery, like I told you to.
难道我就把自己连接到插座上
Oh, I'm just supposed to hook myself up to an outlet,
好像我是个人体平板电脑那样吗
like I'm some sort of human tablet?
要么你给手铐充电
Either you charge the cuffs,
要么你再变回冰霜
or you go all Frozone on us again.
或者你帮我修好它
Or... you could fix them for me?
或者我可以修好它
Or I could fix 'em.
-华丽的一天  同伴们  -天呐
- Sumptuous day, brethren. - Oh, boy.
-早上好  HR  -不止是好
- Good morning, H.R. - Oh, not just good.
是好到不行  为什么呢
It's g-r-r-eat, and why is that?
因为我终于要宣布
Because I'm finally ready to announce
新尖端科研实验室博物馆准备开放了
that the new S.T.A.R. Labs museum is ready for its opening--
小型开张典礼  来吧
soft opening-- so come.
到处转转
Let's take the tour.
这本来可以避免的  知道吗
This could've been avoided. You know that, right?
中城警局
我只是不明白你为什么维护那个黄衣小子
I just don't see why you're defending the yellow guy.
闪电侠去哪  他都跟着
Yes, he goes everywhere The Flash goes,
但是举个例子  今早他就站在那里
but this morning, for example, he's just standing back,
看着仓库被烧毁
waiting for the warehouse to burn down.
也许他在和闪电侠一起特训
Well, maybe he's training with The Flash.
-熟悉情况  -我们派一些
- You know, learning the ropes? - Okay, well, we send
菜鸟警察去巡逻  期待他们的表现
rookie cops out on patrol, expect them to perform.
我觉得黄衣小子会让你惊讶的
Look, I think the yellow guy's gonna surprise you.
只要他吸取一点经验后
Once he gains a little bit of experience,
他就能和闪电侠一较高下
he's gonna give The Flash a run for his money.
知道我的想法吗  我想他也许根本不够快
You know what I think? I think maybe he's just not that fast.
-或许他只是个懦夫  -没人付钱让你想
- Or maybe he's just a coward. - You don't get paid to think.
-闪电小子不是懦夫  -闪电小子  好吧
- And Kid Flash ain't no coward. - Kid Flash? Okay.
这就对了  名字说明了一切
There it is. The name says it all.
不如我们把他送回楔石城
Hey, I say we just send him to Keystone.
我们已经有一个闪电侠了
We already have a Flash.
沃利
Wally.
-你听到那些话了吗  -听到了什么
- Did you hear any of that? - Any of what?
没什么  只是一个警察在犯傻而已
Nothing, it was just a cop being stupid.
-带你去吃早餐  -好
- Take you to breakfast? - Please.
你们看看
Behold.
-这都是你弄的吗  -是的
- You did all this? - Yeah.
功劳不全是我的
Well, I don't wanna take all the credit.
我太谦虚了  但是我做的
I'm too modest to do that, but yeah.
这些钱到底是谁在支付
Uh, who exactly is paying for all this?
这是个好问题
That's a great question.
奥尔加
Olga!
让我给你介绍一下你的新同事
Allow me to introduce you to your new coworkers.
各位  这位是奥尔加
Everybody, this is Olga.
-是  -你好
- Da. - Hi.
她不太说英文
Oh, and she doesn't really speak English so much,
但是人很棒  这边呢
but she's great. So right over here,
我们有门票和入场券
we have the ticketing and the admissions.
那边有我们特色的咖啡
Over there, our specialty coffees--
这提醒了我  凯特琳
Oh, uh, that reminds me. Caitlin...
首先  我本想让你负责票务
Initially, I had you targeted for ticketing,
但是这让我想到  学学如何拉花
but it occurs to me, with a few lessons in foam art,
你就可以完全掌控
you could very well man up-- excuse me-- woman up
我们的卡布奇诺了  你觉得如何
our cappuccino stand. What do you think?
HR  我觉得凯特琳有很多事要做
H.R., I think Caitlin's gonna have plenty to do as it is.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
你们想余生的每一顿都吃冷冻披萨吗
Do you want to eat pizza pockets for every meal
你们不想这样  没人想这样
for the rest of your life? You don't; nobody wants that.
你们要有经济来源
What you want is an income,
我们所有的人都要帮忙支付一些
and we collectively need a cover for S.T.A.R. Labs
尖端实验室的运作费用
for our continued operation.
他说得对
He makes some good points.
轮到代表作品出场
Now for the pièce de résistance...
欢迎来到尖端实验室
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
抱歉  你做了个我的全息投影吗
I'm sorry, did you make a hologram of me?
弗朗西斯科  你说的很清楚
Oh, Francisco, you made it perfectly clear
你不想当导游
you didn't want to be a tour guide.
所以你就不是  你是虚拟导游
You're not. You're a virtual tour guide.
你猜怎么  这也属于
Guess what. That falls under the umbrella
不想当导游的范畴内
of not wanting to be a tour guide.
-开始吧  -我的名字是弗朗西斯科·拉蒙
- On we go. - My name is Francisco Ramon.
我不总是你看到的这个受人尊敬的工程师
I wasn't always the esteemed engineer you see before you.
是我对科学的热爱
It was my love of science
让我经受住了严酷的教育
that allowed me to overcome my tough upbringing
并且加入尖端科研实验室  在我们美丽
and join S.T.A.R. Labs, before our beautiful
并且英俊的创建人  哈里森·威尔斯退休前
and handsome founder, Harrison Wells, stepped down.
我希望我对科学的爱能激发你们
I hope my love of science will inspire some among you
加入科学界的兴趣
to join the scientific community.
谢谢
Thanks.
问题在这
Here's the thing.
我完全不是那样讲话的
I don't sound anything like that.
我对科学的爱  我对科学的爱
My love of science-- my love of science...
我对  科学  的爱
My...love...of...science.
我得需要你帮我调一调
Yeah, I'm gonna need you to take a look at that.
我不行
I can't do it...
因为我还有更重要的事情要做  所以
'Cause I have important things to do, so--
-什么  你...  -所以我就...
- Oh, wha--oh, hey! Ugh! - Right now, so...
各位  我有件事要办  先走了
Guys, I gotta run an errand. See ya later.
你又去哪
Where you going?
-你好呀  -你好
- Ah, hello you. - Hey.
我又要被绑架了吗
Am I in for another kidnapping?
好吧  这是我应得的
Okay, I deserve that.
不  我只是来看看你的
No, um, I just came to check on you.
我们在圣诞节后就没怎么见过你了
We haven't seen much of you since Christmas.
你真好  我过得挺好  谢谢你
That's very sweet of you. I'm doing well, thank you.
你知道  萨维塔做的那事  逼你伤害别人
You know, what Savitar did-- forcing you to hurt people--
萨维塔控制了我  好吗
Savitar was controlling me, okay?
就我来说  我没有道德负担
As far as I'm concerned, my conscience is clear.
真的吗
Really?
那这安眠药做什么的  睡不着觉吗
Then why the Zolpidem? Are you having trouble sleeping?
别再玩游戏了  斯诺博士
Why don't we stop playing games, Dr. Snow,
告诉我你来这里做什么
and you tell me what you actually came for
别在这责难我的失眠症
rather than accusing me of having insomnia?
其实我需要你的帮助
I actually need your help.
我要怎么帮你
How can I help you?
你是世界上首席超能力者专家
Well, you're the world's foremost specialist on meta-humans...
是的  这是事实
Yes, this much is true.
而我需要你帮我摆脱我的能力
And I need you to help me get rid of my powers.
我尝试了一切
I've tried everything.
我做了测试  血液  基因
I've run every test-- blood, DNA--
但就是不能逆转
and I can't reverse this.
我需要摆脱我的能力  以免再...
I need to get rid of my powers before...
以免什么
Before what?
以免我伤害别人  就像对你做的那样
Before I hurt someone else... the way I hurt you.
我不治疗超能力者
I don't cure meta-humans.
我把他们关进监狱
I put them in prison.
你要靠自己了  恐怕
You're on your own, I'm afraid.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
千万别
Please.
好了
Okay.
我能睁开眼睛了吗
Can I open my eyes yet please?
好  但先等一下
Um, yeah, but just one second.
-好的  -就...
- Okay. - Just, um...
好了  睁开眼睛吧
yeah--okay, open 'em.
我知道你想慢慢的收拾好这一切
I know you wanted to unpack slowly,
就像普通情侣一样  但我不确定
like a normal couple, but I don't know--
我们有工作还有尖端实验博物馆
between our jobs and the S.T.A.R. Labs museum and--
你讨厌吗
do you hate it?
不不  我不讨厌
Uh, n-no, no, I don't hate it.
你讨厌  我就是  我不...
You do. I just--I don't--
我只是想要给你个应得的家
I just wanna give you the home that you deserve.
-我...  -巴里  你已经给了
- I... - Barry, you have.
我爱我们的小阁楼
I love our loft.
听着  我不喜欢的
Look... what I don't love
是你不和我谈论那些恶梦
is you not talking to me about these nightmares.
我不知道  我是说  我这一生
I don't know. I mean, I've seen
看到过不少可怕的事情
a lot of terrible things in my life.
那些恶梦  它们只是我的一部分
The nightmares, they're just a part of me.
没错  但是巴里  我和你一起
Yeah, but, Barry, I have been with you
经历了那些可怕的事情
through all those terrible things.
这次不一样
This is different.
感觉不一样
It feels different.
你有什么没告诉我
What are you not telling me?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是个正在进行中的抢劫
Oh, that's a robbery in progress.
That is a robbery in progress.
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
去吧
Go.
我现在和人一起住
See, I'm living with someone now,
所以我不能总让罪犯不停地打断
so I can't have criminals constantly interrupting
我们独处的时间
our alone time.
闪电侠
Flash.
莫里罗被闪电侠抓获
Morillo was found guilty
突发新闻
杰sx拉德·莫里罗定罪
他因重大盗窃
of grand theft and aggravated assault
突发新闻
杰sx拉德·莫里罗定罪
和故意伤害被判有罪
after he was caught by The Flash.
那把枪
That gun.
我从来没见过像那样的东西
I've never seen anything like that in my life.
-我想要一把那样的枪  -发生了什么
- I want a gun like that. - What happened out there?
你的遥感数据急速下降
Your telemetry readings dropped precipitously.
我不知道  但是
I don't know, but...
我被打了个措手不及
It caught me off-guard.
我现在有事出去一下  马上回来
I've gotta run an errand. I'll be right back.
好吧  所以我们现在是要跟一个拿着高级枪
Okay, so we're up against a guy with a futuristic rifle
偷珠宝还长得像海盗的人干上了
that steals jewelry and looks like a pirate.
海盗  好吧
A pirate. Right, then...
那我们就给这个坏孩子
we shall call this scurvy lad boy
起名叫掠夺  掠夺  怎么样
the name of Plunder. Plunder, agreed?
突发新闻
杰sx拉德·莫里罗定罪
杰拉德·莫里罗  即"掠夺"
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder...
你难道不应该去忙
Okay, aren't you supposed to be working on, like,
-你的博物馆什么的吗  -你难道不应该
- your museum, or something? - Aren't you supposed to be
来帮我弄全息投影吗  弗朗西斯科
helping me, Francisco, with me hologram?
那才不关我的事
Um, that's not my problem.
我就想给你看个东西
Yeah, I just wanna show you something.
为什么我感觉我在往坑里走
Why do I feel like I'm walking into a trap?
不管怎样  我会让中城警局监控
Anyway, I'm gonna get CCPD to monitor
城里所有的珠宝商铺
all the jewelry stores in the city.
他从闪电侠手中逃走
This guys must be pretty full of himself,
一定非常自得  所以他肯定会回来
knowing he escaped The Flash, so ten to one, he'll be back.
-好的  -他回来的时候
- All right. - When he is,
我们就能准备好了  对吧  巴里
we'll be ready for him, though, right, Barry?
不  不是我们  沃利
No, not we, Wally.
你还在训练
This--you're still training.
你最近看到我在极速实验室的状态了吗
Have you seen my times in the Speed Lab lately?
-我基本和你一样快了  -这不是速度的问题
- I’m almost as fast as you. - Okay, this isn't about speed.
而是要积累知识和经验
This is about gaining knowledge and experience,
所以请你相信我  好吗
so please just trust me, all right?
我是这世界上过度保护欲最强的父亲了
Look, I am as overprotective a father as you can get,
但我得说实话  巴里
but I gotta be honest, Barry,
我赞成沃利
I'm--I agree with Wally.
我说不好  乔  在对沃利放手前
I don't know, Joe. Let's just see what else
还是先看看我们能找到这个人的什么信息吧
we can find on this guy before we let Wally loose.
好吧  不过记住  教一个人的最好办法
Okay, well, remember, the best way
就是把那个人丢进绝境
to teach somebody something is to throw them in the deep end.
我就是这么教你游泳的
That's how I taught you how to swim.
那真是  我现在还是很生气
That was-- I'm still mad about that.
你现在会游泳了  对不对
You can swim now, can't you?
对
Yeah.
中城警局
我收到你的短信了
Got your text.
你好  过来坐吧
Hi. Come and take a seat.
听着  我知道  我昨天很没礼貌
Look, I--I know I was... rude yesterday.
是啊  你昨天可是个顶级混蛋
Yeah, you were a world-class jerk.
也有这个原因
Yeah, there is a reason.
因为你就是个顶级混蛋吗
Because you are a world-class jerk?
也有道理
Fair enough.
我一直很努力地让自己不要去想
Listen, I've been trying really hard not to think
另一个我  以及他做了什么
about my alter ego, about what he did,
看到你之后  那些
and seeing you, it just...
那些感觉全回来了
it brought it all back.
听着
Look,
炼金术师的所为不是你的错
what Alchemy did was not your fault.
你把这话告诉戴夫·弗里曼  本·爱德华兹和乔治·冈萨雷斯去
Tell that to Dave Frieman, Ben Edwards, Jorge Gonzales.
他们都是中城警局特别小组中
These men were part of the CCPD task force
被萨维塔杀掉的人
that Savitar murdered.
该死的是我  不是他们
I should've died, not them.
朱利安  你现在的感受很正常
Julian, what you're feeling, it's completely normal.
这叫幸存者的负罪感
It's called survivor's guilt.
但那不是你的错  好吗
But it wasn't your fault, okay?
你也是受害者
You're a victim too.
我折磨别人
I--I tortured people
还差点杀了我最好的朋友
and nearly killed my best friends.
我不想要这些能力
I didn't ask for these powers,
就和你不想被萨维塔利用一样
just like you didn't ask to be used by Savitar.
是啊
Yeah.
我只是不知道怎么翻过这一页
I just don't know how to move forward.
不如来尖端实验室加入我们
Why don't you come join us at S.T.A.R. Labs?
你可以帮闪电侠小组打击超能力者
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
-你是认真的吗  -是啊
- You're being serious? - Yeah.
如果你来  巴里和团队里的人会很高兴的
Barry and the team, they'd be thrilled to have you.
我也很高兴你加入我们
I would be thrilled to have you.
我会考虑一下
I'll give it some thought.
感谢你过来
Thanks for coming.
告诉我我为什么要来这修你的全息图
Tell me why I'm in here fixing your hologram.
只因我太有说服力了  事实上
Well, I'm just so persuasive. As a matter of fact,
我的地球上的搭档兰道夫过去常说
my partner on my Earth, Randolf, used to say,
"怎么回事  HR  你竟然能说服
"Why, H.R., you could convince a cowboy
牛仔在沙暴中买下尘土"  来杯卡布奇诺
to buy dirt in a sandstorm." Cappuccino?
你不是才喝了一杯吗
Didn't you just have one of those?
对
Oh, yeah.
听着  修这个我得再订些零件
Look, I gotta order more parts for this thing.
好的  去吧  价钱不是问题
Yeah, no, go ahead. Price is no object.
怎么样了
How's it going?
尖端科研实验室博物馆
You know, S.T.A.R. Labs museum,
事情忙不完  所以
gift that keeps on giving, so...
-好吧  -巴里  喝杯卡布奇诺
- Okay. - Barry, cappuccino.
-不用了  -好吧  没事
- Hi, uh, no--uh, good. - Okay--all right.
-抱歉  -那两杯一起喝
- Sorry. - You know I'll double down.
-好吧  -没事
- Yeah, no-- - Sure.
我其实还真有事要问你
Um, I just actually wanted to ask you something...
就是你的科学
about your scientific, uh,
-言情小说  -我的小说  问吧
- romance novels? - Oh, my novels, yeah, sure.
-请坐  问吧  -好
- Please, ha--have a seat, yeah. - Okay.
想问什么问什么  什么都可以
Ask any--anything you want. Any questions.
-好的  太好了  -没错
- Yep--all right, cool. - Yeah.
我只是在想你有没有写过时间旅行
I was just wondering  if you've ever written about time travel.
具体点说写穿越到未来的故事
But more specifically traveling to the future.
不  我的畅销作品
Oh, no, my best seller-- oh, hey,
《未来迥非旧颜》
"The Future Ain't What It Used to Be"--
那全是
that was--
写的故事是关于某个人
it was all about-- it was all about this guy
努力预防自己被杀
who's actively trying to prevent his own murder.
获得了星云奖  大受欢迎
Won the Nebula Award. It's well-received.
对
Yeah.
所以这个角色  你塑造的角色
Um, so this character-- your character--
他有能力改变自己的未来吗
uh, was he able to change his future?
更具体点说  如果他让某些事自然发生
More specifically, if he allowed certain events to occur naturally,
那他只是在加固以后会导致
was he only cementing the very timeline
可怕事件的那条时间线吗
that resulted in a horrible event later?
有两种看法
There were two schools of thought.
有一派粉丝  他们认为
One faction--one group of fans--they believed,
未来变化莫测
you know, the future's ever-changing.
并不是固定的  所以
You know, it's not fixed, and so
你可以按自己的意愿创造未来
you could make of the future anything you wish.
-好  -另一派粉丝
- Right. - Another group of fans
坚决不同意这点  他们表示"不不不
vehemently disagreed with it. They said, "No, no, no.
未来是固定的  不论多么努力
The future is fixed, and you can't change it
都没法改变"
no matter how hard you try."
你是站在哪边的
Where do you come down?
固定不变还是变化莫测的未来
On a fixed or ever-changing future?
我认为人类常常在为了逃避某个命运
Well, I think that a man often meets his destiny
而选择的道路上直面自己的命运
on the very road he takes to avoid it.
-什么意思  -意思是
- Meaning? - Meaning...
-未来是固定的  -好吧
- the future is fixed. - Yeah.
各位  佩森酒店发生抢劫
Yo, there's a robbery at the Payson Hotel.
-去吧  -好
- Go. - Yeah.
让直升机飞回来
Bring that chopper back.
你就是忍不住再次抢劫吧
You just couldn't resist another heist, huh?
一次定输赢的乐趣在哪
Oh, what's the fun in one and done?
不用在铁山监狱蹲十五年
Avoiding a 15-year jail sentence
本来还挺好的
in Iron Heights would've been nice,
但你这是逼我出手
but you're forcing my hand.
我猜现在有点来不及了
I guess it's a little late for that now.
再猜
Eh, guess again.
巴里  在你后面
Barry, behind you!
我甩不掉这些玩意  西斯科
I can't shake these things, Cisco.
-甩快点  -什么
- Shake faster. - Huh?
他是说穿过去
He means phase.
巴里  你在等什么
Barry, what are you waiting for?
突发新闻
杰拉德·莫里罗被判有罪
被闪电侠抓获之后
After he was caught by The Flash...
小心
Watch out!
不  沃利
No, Wally.
我全都拍下来了  哥们
I caught that whole thing, man.
想对镜头说点什么吗
Anything you wanna say to camera?
真的吗
Oh, for real?
大家好  中城居民  我叫闪电小子
Uh, what up, Central City? The name's Kid Flash.
沃利  祝贺  太棒了
Wally, congratulations. That was amazing.
干得漂亮  沃利
Great job, Wally.
闪电小子  名声大噪
Kid Flash! Let 'em know.
就是这么来的
That's how it's done.
我们把掠夺送到铁山监狱了
We just deposited Plunder in Iron Heights.
-没错  -他的真名是杰拉德·莫里罗
- Yes, you did. - His real name is Jared Morillo.
结果发现他因为
Turns out he's wanted
一系列抢劫案被这里和星城通缉
for a string of robberies from here to Star City.
沃利  刚才怎么回事
Wally, what was that?
你不应该出头的
I mean, you're supposed to be shadowing me.
等等  你生我的气了  我以为...
Wait, you're mad at me? I thought--
观察和学习  只有这些
Observe and learn. That's it.
只有这些
That's it!
巴里  别激动  沃利刚救了你的命
Barry, ease up. Wally just saved your life.
抱歉  沃利  但如果你学不会服从命令
I'm sorry, Wally, but if you can't learn to follow orders,
我俩的约定就取消
this deal between us, it's over.
好啦  谁准备好去...
Okay. Who's ready for--
天  华莱士  BA
oh, man. Wallace, B.A.,
你们应该为博物馆开幕式穿好礼服
you're supposed to be dressed for the museum opening.
HR  我们是极速者  我们有的是时间
H.R., we're speedsters. We have time.
-没有人喜欢吹牛大王  -是  但是我们
- Nobody likes a braggart. - Yeah, but we were actually
在你闯进来之前在讨论重要的事情
talking about something important before you showed up,
-所以说... -你
- so... - You--
-不错  你收拾干净了  -谢了
- Okay, you clean up well... - Thank you.
我喜欢你的风格
I like the way you dress.
大伙儿  这对我们所有人来说是件大事
Guys, this is a very, very big deal for all of us.
快点  来派对不要迟到哦
Come on! Don't be late to the part-ay!
沃利
Wally.
听着  我要去中城警局
Look, I'm gonna go over to CCPD
填完莫里罗的报告
and fill out this Morillo paperwork.
不管你因为什么对沃利发火
Whatever the reasoning you have, for ragging on Wally,
-拜托克服一下  -嗯
- please get over it. - Mm.
凯特琳
Caitlin
人都去哪了  没有人来
where is everybody? Nobody's here.
没一个人来
No one showed up.
顾客...我们前两位顾客
A custom--our first customers!
欢迎  欢迎来到盛大的
Welcome. Welcome to the grand
尖端科研实验室博物馆开幕式
S.T.A.R. Labs museum opening,
今天  你们的入场票价
and today, for your ticket price of admission--
只有今天  还可以得到一杯免费咖啡
today only--you also get a free steaming cup of joe.
-票价  -是的
- Ticket price? - Yep.
我以为进博物馆是免费的
I thought this museum was free.
你是通过社交媒体找过来的吗  因为
did you find us through social media? 'Cause--
欢迎...
Welcome--welcome...
-奥尔加  -在
- Olga! - Da.
这东西  出问题了
- The thing-- it's doing the thing.
大伙儿  不  等等
Folks, no--wait, do--oh!
等等  不  半价  半价  两折...
Wait--no, wait, half-price! Half! Quarter--
我做一杯新咖啡
I'll make a new pot of coffee.
-不用麻烦了  -没有人来了
- Don't bother. - No one's coming.
这行不通  我不知道为什么
This isn't working. I don't know why.
你看到了吗
You see this?
你看到你做了什么了吗  HR
Do you see what you've done, H.R.?
你让我们分心了这么多个月  怎样呢
You have distracted us for months, so what?
这样你可感到有用武之地吗  你没有用
So that you could feel useful? You're not useful.
这个博物馆也一无是处
This museum isn't useful.
你知道吗
You know what?
-这样真刻薄  -好啊  我想
- That's mean. - Yeah, well, I guess
我是从你的二重身那里学来的
I learned that from your doppelganger,
而且至少他有所贡献
and at least he contributed something.
伙计们  又来了一位客人
guys, there's another customer.
欢迎来到尖...是朱利叶斯  伙计们
Hey, welcome to S-- ah, it's Julius, you guys.
你来这儿做什么
What are you doing here?
我考虑了一下
Well, uh, I've given it some thought,
我想接受你的邀请
and I'd like to accept your invitation.
什么邀请
Invitation for what?
你邀请朱利安加入
Did you ask Julian to join
尖端科研实验室团队
Team S.T.A.R. Labs?
我明白  我们对他的印象逐渐好转  但是
I know, he's an acquired taste, but--
他是炼金术师
Yeah, well, he is Dr. Alchemy,
大坏蛋手下的小坏蛋
the big bad's little bad, so...
是  他给了沃利他的超能力
Yeah, he--he gave Wally his powers.
-这我不介意  -我需要他的帮助
- That, I don't mind. - Guys, I need his help.
抱歉  西斯科  但是这手铐阻止不了的
I'm sorry, Cisco, but these cuffs, they aren't cutting it.
每晚我睡觉时
Every night, when I go to bed,
我都害怕我起来时
I'm afraid that I'm gonna wake up...
会是她
be her.
也许朱利安可以想到我们没想到的办法
Maybe Julian can think of something that we haven't.
巴里
Barry...
当你的妈妈被谋杀时
when your mom was murdered,
乔和爱瑞丝收留了你
Joe and Iris, they took you in.
西斯科  当丹堤去世时
Cisco, when Dante died,
我睡在沙发上陪你
I slept on your couch to keep you company.
我们看到的事情  面对的事情
The things we see, the things that we face...
没人可以独自承受
no one can do this alone.
试着一个人承受是最大的错误
Trying is the biggest mistake that you can make.
他没有告诉任何人巴里是闪电侠
He hasn't told anyone that Barry's The Flash.
我认为我们可以给他一个机会
I think we can give him a chance.
告诉朱利安我们会考虑的  好吗
Tell Julian we'll think about it, all right?
爱瑞丝
Iris...
我得让你看样东西
I need to show you something.
-我都忘了这个地方的存在  -是啊
- I forgot this place existed. - Yeah.
以前的威尔斯把它称作时间穹顶
The original Wells used to call it his time vault.
我最近经常到这里来
I've been coming down here a lot lately.
我猜我已经
I guess I've
变得像他以前一样痴迷于未来
become as obsessed with the future as he once was.
闪电侠在危机中消失
闪点事件后  这篇文章又出现了
After Flashpoint happened, this article reappeared.
闪电侠消失...
"Flash Missing...
于危机中  朱莉·格瑞尔
Vanishes In Crisis." Julie Greer,
2024年4月25日
April 25, 2024.
署名以前是爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
The byline used to read "Iris West-Allen.
未来改变了
The future's changed.
可能是我辞职了
So maybe I quit my job.
对  我一开始我也这么希望
Yeah, that's what I'd hoped at first too,
或者是其他情况
or something,
但我...
but I...
爱瑞丝  抱歉之前没有告诉你
Look, Iris, I'm sorry I didn't tell you this sooner.
我把魔法石丢到神速力里之后
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone into the Speed Force,
我偶然地跑入了未来
I accidentally ran to the future.
我看到萨维塔杀了你
I saw Savitar murder you.
而我看到我自己
And I saw myself, and I--
没法跑得那么快去救你
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
巴里  不  我是说  我们
Barry, no--I mean, we--
我们毁掉了魔法石  萨维塔消失了
We destroyed the Stone. Savitar's gone, so...
也许并没有  我
Maybe not. I--
我不清楚  也许并没有
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe not.
所以你一直做噩梦吗
Is that why you keep having nightmares?
一直在梦里看到我吗
You keep seeing me?
这和"掠夺"有什么关系呢
So what does this have to do with Plunder?
未来他已经在监狱了
He was already in jail in the future,
我不知道  我觉得如果我没抓住他
so I don't know. I thought if I didn't catch him,
就可以阻止时间线接合
that I could stop the timeline from cementing.
你就不会死  我不知道
I could prevent your death. I don't know.
巴里  你不能为了救我而不去保护这座城市
Barry, you cannot stop protecting the city to save me.
为什么  为什么不可能
Why? Um, why not?
抱歉  一个强盗逍遥法外
I'm sorry. Uh, one robber goes free.
与你生命的重要性根本无法相提并论
It's that versus your life.
乔也会希望我这么做的  爱瑞丝
Joe would want me to make the exact same choice, Iris.
他
He--
爱瑞丝
Iris.
-多久  -什么多久
- How long? - How long what?
我还能活多久
How long until it happens?
我不会让这一切发生的
This is not gonna happen.
看着我  这不会发生的
Hey, look at me. This is not gonna happen.
杰伊说过你的死只是未来的一种可能性
Jay said that your death is just one possible future, okay?
所以我们有4个月时间搞清楚
So that gives us four months to figure out
怎么阻止萨维塔
how to stop Savitar.
我用我父母的生命起誓
I swear, on both my parents' lives,
我会保护你
I will protect you.
我们不能独自面对这事  巴里
We can't do this alone, Barry.
大伙们
Hey, guys, um...
爱瑞丝和我
Iris and I, um...
有一些事需要告诉你们
we have something we need to tell you.
你是说4个月之后
So you're saying that four months from now,
-萨维塔会...  -杀了我
- Savitar will... - Kill me.
有可能
Possi--possibly.
没事的  我没事的  真的
It's okay. Guys, I am okay. Really.
-你要怎么跟爸爸说呢  -我不会说的
- How are you gonna tell Dad? - I'm not.
爱瑞丝  他需要知道
Iris, he needs to know.
我同意华莱士  乔得知道这事
I agree with Wallace. Joe needs to know.
不  这件事会让他失去判断力  好吗
No, guys, this news would blind him, okay?
沃利陷入危机时  我们都见到他有多疯狂了
We all saw how crazy he went when Wally was in danger.
再试想他得知萨维塔会杀了我会是什么反应
Imagine if he knew that Savitar was trying to kill me.
他会独自去追击萨维塔
He would go after Savitar himself.
沃利...
Wally...
未来还没被设定  仍有希望
The future isn't set. There's still hope.
不  巴里  未来
But, Barry, the future,
比你想象中更难改变
it's harder to change than you can imagine.
未来想要这件事发生  那我的理解就是
The future wants to happen. The way it was explained to me
假设你有一排多米诺骨牌
was, imagine if you had a row of dominos, okay?
现在多米诺骨牌都排好了  这...
Now, those dominos are all set up, and it--it's--
给你
Here.
正是时候  巴里  如果你...
So convenient--yeah-- uh, Barry, if you wou--
设想
So imagine, okay,
每块骨牌都是一个时刻
domino--each domino is a moment in time.
每一个时刻引导向下一个时刻
One moment in time leads to the next,
一块骨牌倒下  撞击到下一块
so as one domino falls, it hits the next,
一张接着一张
it hits the next, and the next, and the next, and so on,
引导向无法避免的结论  那就是...
leading to the inevitable conclusion, and that is...
未来
The future.
如果我们改变某个结果会发生什么事呢
And what happens if we alter certain events?
你是可以
Well, you-- you could conceivably
改变结果的  但...
change where you end up, but--
但  巴里  如果你可以
but, Barry, if you would--
就可以改变未来
So you could change the future,
但你得非常小心
but you'd have to be very careful
具体要改变哪一个...
about which events...
事件
you alter.
我们必须弄清导致爱瑞丝死亡的
We need to figure out everything that happens
每一个诱因
leading up to Iris's death.
我看到未来电视上播了一则滚动新闻
Wait, when I saw the future, there was a news scroll on TV.
这可能提供一些线索给我们
I mean, that could offer us some clues.
没错  我可以帮上忙
Absolutely. I think I can help with that.
坐稳了  小飞侠
Hang on, McFly.
我要把你震波到未来去了
About to vibe you back to the future.
-能把万用表递给我吗  -好的
- Can you pass me the multi-meter please? - Yeah.
-万用表  -好
- The multi-meter. - Yep.
-万用表  -好的
- The multi-meter? - Yeah.
我更熟悉文士的工具
I'm better with the tools of the scribe.
这个是
There it is.
你确定你搭档兰道夫破解密码
You sure your buddy Randolf back home didn't just
不是为了摆脱你吗
solve that cryptogram to get rid of you?
也许是的
perhaps he did.
我来这个地球寻求救赎  但是
Look, I came to this Earth seeking redemption,but
我现在明白了  你是对的
I realize now, you're right.
我身上并没有什么伟大之处
Greatness isn't in the cards for me.
好吧
Okay.
所以你失败了  没人来你的开幕式
So you failed. So nobody came to your opening.
但别这样就结束
Don't end it like this.
伟大是需要时间的
Greatness takes time...
你是知道的
and you know this.
如果绳子打了死结  唯有耐心方能解开
If a string is in a knot, patience will untie it.
耐心可以实现很多事
Patience can do lots of things.
你试过这么做吗
Have you ever tried it?
好吧
All right.
好了  你们准备好了吗
All right, guys. You ready?
-好了  -我们准备好了
- Yeah. - Yeah, we're ready.
机器加大了马力  蓄势待发
The machine's souped up and ready to go.
这肯定是次前所未有的震波
It's gonna be a hell of a vibe.
你要做的就是坐稳  放松
All you have to do is just sit back, relax--
或者说尽量放松
or, well, try to relax--
集中注意  专心回想
and concentrate, really focus
你之前穿越到未来的具体日期
on the exact date in the future that you traveled to.
好的
Yep.
2017年5月23日
May 23, 2017.
巴里  无论发生什么
Barry, whatever happens,
我都会在这里等着你  知道吗
I am right here waiting for you, okay?
知道
I know.
-开启吧  -三二一
- Crank it. - Three, two, one.
你看到什么了
What do you see?
空荡的街道
An empty street.
一个公交站
A bus stop.
圣诞节时的我刚从神速力里出来
The me from Christmas just came out of the Speed Force.
另一条法律新闻  "掠夺"...
In other legal news, the highly publicized trial...
他正在看新闻报道
He's watching the news report.
备受关注的审讯已经结束
AKA Plunder, comes to a close.
莫里罗因重大盗窃
Morillo was found guilty
和故意伤害被判有罪...
of grand theft and aggravated assault...
这些是滚动头条吧
These are the headlines, right?
滚动头条  有办法了
Headlines. Yeah--you know what?
把它们念出来  我记下来
Call--call 'em out. I'll write 'em down.
"音乐大师取得了六位数的出书合约"
"Music Meister gets six-figure book deal."
"路易餐厅在谋杀案后重新开张"
"Luigi's opens after murder."
"乔·韦斯特在市政厅授勋"
"Joe West honored at City Hall."
干得不错  乔
Good for you, Joe.
"冰霜..."
"Killer"...
上面说了什么
What does it say?
"冰霜杀手仍然逍遥法外"
"Killer Frost still at large."
"尖端科研实验室博物馆倒闭"
"S.T.A.R. Labs museum closes."
"遭到大猩猩袭击后  城市还在重建中"
"City still recovering following gorilla attack."
不要
Don't!
爱瑞丝在萨维塔手上
Savitar has Iris.
不要这么做
Don't do this.
现在  我终于摆脱你的禁锢了
Now finally, I am free of you.
看  房顶上
Look, up on the roof.
巴里  我爱你
Barry... I love you.
不  别说这话  知道吗
Hey, no, don't say that, all right?
-HR在这里  -我吗  你确定吗
- H.R. is here. - Me? Are you sure?
-是的  你之前不在场  -未来从那时起改变了
- Yeah, you weren't here before. - Future's changed since then.
你输了  巴里
You lose, Barry.
不
No!
快把我们弄出去
Just get us out of here.
你拿着步枪对准萨维塔
You had a rifle pointed at Savitar.
告诉你爱瑞丝的死
Somehow telling you about Iris's death,
不知怎样  改变了未来
it changed the future.
我错了  你是对的  你当时的理论是对的
I was wrong, you were right. Your theory is correct then.
各位  我们要改变的不只有我的未来
Guys, my future isn't the only one that we need to change.
不  那些滚动头条
No, the--these headlines, though,
它们告诉我们未来发生了什么
they--they tell us what happens in the future--
凯特琳变成了冰霜杀手  爱瑞丝死了
where Caitlin becomes Killer Frost and Iris dies.
如果我们可以改变那些头条
If we can change the headlines,
也就是说我们能改变未来
that means we can change the future.
没错  接受挑战
That's right. Challenge accepted.
爸爸在楼上  我们在找你
Dad's upstairs. We've been looking for you.
发生什么事了
What happened?
"掠夺"逃跑了
Plunder escaped.
莫里罗在去铁山监狱的路上袭击了两名押送员
Morillo assaulted two guards on his way out of Iron Heights.
知道他接下来会在哪里下手吗
Any idea where he might strike next?
我们把范围缩小到中城的
Well, we've got it narrowed down to 35 jewelry stores
35间珠宝店和48家酒店
and 48 hotels in Central City, so...
还有银行和拍卖行呢
What about banks? Auction houses?
今年初他在抢劫
He was caught by The Flash,
突发消息
杰拉德·莫里罗被判有罪
中城博物馆时被闪电侠逮捕
robbing the Central City Museum earlier this year.
中城博物馆
Central City Museum.
-他会去那里  -你怎么想到的
- That's where he is. - Where'd you get that?
-那里在办珠宝展吧  -是的
- Isn't there a jewelry exhibit there right now? - Yeah.
有大颗的钻石  说得通
Uh-huh, with diamonds-- big ones, so it makes sense.
着装准备
Let's suit up.
我不明白
I don't understand.
过来
Come here.
昨天我是混蛋  沃利  跟你无关
I was a dick yesterday, Wally. It wasn't about you.
我害怕你抓到"掠夺"
I was scared when you caught Plunder.
我不知道这会怎么影响爱瑞丝的未来
I didn't know what it meant for Iris's future.
你准备好了
You're ready,
你比我起步时准备得更充分
far more ready than I was when I started.
你觉得呢
What do you say?
-我加入  -好的
- I'm in. - All right.
"掠夺"  老兄  你准备去哪里
Plunder, my man. Where do you think you're going?
穿过你
Right through you.
-你没事吧  -我很好  哥们
- You all right? - I'm good, dude.
这次交给你
You can have this one.
不  沃利  这次必须由你来
No, Wally. This one has to be you.
为什么
Why?
因为如果你抓了"掠夺"
Because if you take down Plunder,
那未来说我抓了他的
the news report that says that I captured him
新闻报道就错了
in the future, it's wrong.
此时此地  我们可以证明
We can prove that we can alter the future
我们能改变未来
here and now.
所以你让我来这里
So that's why you sent me out here.
我让你来这里是因为你是英雄
Hey, I sent you out here because you're a hero.
爱瑞丝现在需要英雄  沃利
Iris needs a hero right now, Wally.
他们在跑着
They are running.
沃利  下个路口转左  前方约3.2公里
Wally, take your next left. The streets meet up
街道会汇合  如果你时间捏准了
in about two miles. If you time it just right,
-你就能偷袭他  -收到
- you'll be able to blindside him. - Got it.
闪电小子  闪电小子
Kid Flash! Kid Flash!
听到了吗  他们在叫你的名字
Do you hear that? They're saying your name.
闪电小子  闪电小子
Kid Flash! Kid Flash!
闪电小子逮捕"掠夺"
今日头条
Today's top story,
企图抢劫中城博物馆的杰拉德·莫里罗
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder, is back in police custody
即"掠夺"  已被警方再次拘留
after attempting to rob the Central City Museum.
莫里罗被一个叫闪电小子的
Morillo was apprehended by a new speedster,
新极速者逮捕
who goes by the name Kid Flash.
就这么定了
Well, that settles it.
我想你现在正式成为闪电小子了
I think you're officially Kid Flash now.
对  这逐渐跟我合为一体了
Yeah, it's growing on me.
而这把步枪逐渐跟我合为一体
And this rifle is growing on me.
热追踪子弹只是
Heat-seeking bullets are just the beginning
这坏家伙的初始功能
of what this bad boy can do.
"掠夺"的步枪怎么在你手里
How did you end up with Plunder's rifle?
巴里偷给我的  对吗  巴仔
Barry stole it for me. Right, Barr?
你掠夺了"掠夺"的东西
Oh, so you plundered Plunder?
沃利在逮捕他时我得做点什么
I had to do something while Wally was cuffing him.
多亏你  我们改变了未来
Thanks to you, we changed the future.
既然我们能改变其中一个事件
If we can change one of these events,
我们就能改变所有事件
we can change 'em all.
没有什么是改变不了的
Nothing is set in stone.
我们今晚见
We'll see you guys tonight.
-迫不及待  -是的
- Can't wait. - Yeah.
我打给了本地的小学
I called the local elementary school,
把折扣票交给校长
and gave the principal discounted tickets.
我认为如果孩子们喜欢这里
I figured, hey, you know, if the kids love it,
他们会告诉他们的父母
they'll tell their parents, and, well,
就像多米诺牌一样
the rest writes itself.
弗朗西斯科  你太聪明了
You, Francisco... are brilliant.
当然  不只是闪电侠
Of course, science
科学也会激发
is what will inspire these children--
这些孩子
not just The Flash.
快看
Check it out.
欢迎来到尖端科研实验室
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
我叫弗朗西斯科·拉蒙
My name is Francisco Ramon.
从前的我并不是备受爱戴的工程师
I wasn't always the esteemed engineer you see before you,
经过多年的努力和学习
but after years of hard work and studying,
我加入了尖端科研实验室
I joined S.T.A.R. Labs.
-希望我对科学的爱  -我们要去跟他谈吗
- I hope my love of science... - Should we go talk to him?
会激发你们当中的一些人
Will inspire some among you
加入科学社区
to join the scientific community
跟我们携手努力迈入人类的新时代
as we strive to reach a new age for humanity.
谢谢
Thank you.
你太客气了
You're very welcome.
乳蛋饼在烤箱里
Okay, the quiche is in the oven;
啤酒和葡萄酒在冰箱里
the beer and wine are in the fridge;
蜡烛在桌上
and the candles are on the table.
-天哪  天哪  -怎么了
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - What?
我忘了冰块
I forgot the ice.
极速派对救星
Instant party save.
宝贝  你今天最性感
Baby, you've never been sexier.
我知道
I know.
爱瑞丝
Hey, Iris.
你还好吗  说真的  你没事吧
How are you doing? For real, are you okay?
-我没事  -如果你有什么事
- Yeah, I'm fine. - Because if you're not fine,
都可以跟我说  知道吧
you can talk to me. You know that, right?
我知道
I know.
好
All right.
-准备好了吗  -好了  -好
- You ready? - Yeah. - All right.
我给你们带了盆栽
I got you guys a plant.
这是标准的乔迁贺礼  对吧
That's like a standard housewarming gift, right?
-没错  完美  -在我的地球不是
- Yes, perfect. - Not on my Earth.
我的地球送的是爬行类
On my Earth, we get reptiles.
我把蜗牛龟送给你
I present to you McSnurtle...
龟类  小心  它会咬人
the turtle. Careful, she bites.
-这是给我的吗  -这是乔迁贺礼
- I--this is for me? - It's for the housewarming.
你俩做得非常好  这里"棒呆"了
You two did really well. This place is "Noice."
谢谢  你好  爸爸
Thank you. Mm, hi, Daddy.
天哪  很完美
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
对吧
Yeah, right?
给你取什么名字呢
What are we gonna call you?
这是我的宠物  你在爬向...
Look, I--I got a pet. Who are you trying--
-你好  -你好
- Hello, hello. - Oh, hey.
你好  希望我没迟到
Hi. I hope I'm not too late.
来得正是时候
Right on time.
很好  这是给你的
Good, good. This is a--it's for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们商量好了
So we all talked it over, and
欢迎加入我们的团队
welcome to the team.
你是认真的吗
You being serious?
-对  -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
我很兴奋  我上一个团队
Yeah, it's so exciting. I mean, my last team,
全被萨维塔杀了
they were all murdered by Savitar, so...
我们要加强你的聊天技巧
We need to work on your small talk skills.
当然  我只是不想隐瞒
Yeah, sure. Just wanted to be upfront.
-进来吧  -谢谢你
- Come on in. - That's nice of you.
-要喝一杯吗  -好啊
- You want a drink? - Uh, yeah, I'd love one.
给我的吗
Is this for me?
-是的  -好
- Oh, yeah. - All right.
这里太棒了  巴仔
This place is incredible, Barr.
谢谢
Thank you.
老实说  我想念你在家里的日子
I have to admit, I miss you around the house.
-是吗  -但有沃利在
- Yeah? - But Wally over there
填补了我的空虚
keeps me plenty occupied.
我已经跟沃利谈过了
Yeah, um, I already talked to Wally,
昨天的事我很抱歉  你是对的
but I'm sorry about yesterday. You were right.
他对我们的团队很重要
He's really important to this team.
他是真正的英雄  乔
He's a real hero, Joe.
我的两个儿子都是英雄
Both of my sons are heroes.
我和朱利安聊了你手铐的
Julian and I were talking about your battery problem
电池问题
with your cuffs.
我们决定给你加件配饰
we decided we'd invest in an alternate accessory.
看吧
Voilà.
只要你在室外  就能给它充太阳能
Every time you go outside, solar energy will recharge it.
各位
Guys,
这对我意义重大  谢谢
this means so much to me. Thank you.
不客气
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
各位
Hey, guys.
我想在这种场合说几句话
I asked myself to say a few words, um, on this occasion.
一个家  不只是由砖块  灰泥和
A home, you know, it's more than bricks and mortar
龟组成  这是种感觉
and a turtle. It's a--it's a feeling.
是归属感  不是吗
It's a feeling of belonging, isn't it?
是爱  没错
Of--of love, of course--
未来的希望
hope for the future.
我想
I don't know
我还没见过
if I have ever met two people
比你俩更般配的伴侣
who are more suited to one another than you two.
-祝贺巴里和爱瑞丝  -巴里和爱瑞丝
- To Barry and Iris. - Barry and Iris.
祝贺巴里和爱瑞丝
To Barry and Iris.
-祝贺我们  -祝贺我们
- To us. - To us.